0

snigdha464@gmail.com

Human Resources Executive

<u>Snigdha Mishra</u>

Noida, Uttar Pradesh



SUMMARY

Passionate HR professional with over 4+ years of experience, excited to elevate HR strategies for your dynamic team and play a pivotal role in achieving company objectives. I look forward to connecting and discussing how my skills and dedication can bring value to your organization.

EDUCATION

Utkal University

Master's in Business Administration Human Resource Management 2017 – 2019

Salipur College

Bachelor's in Science, PCM 2012 – 2015

SKILLS

- Strong communication and people management skills.
- Ability to learn quickly & effectively.
- Proficient in MS Word Excel, PowerPoint & outlook.
- Basic understanding of recruitment process & payroll compliance.
- Experienced in managing employee and community programs & Capable of conducting employee's engagement activities.

LANGUANGE

- English.
- Hindi.
- Odia.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certification course in Human Resources Management.

Udemy

Issued in September 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Human Resources Executive

Sudha Fin-Por Services, Bhubaneswar, | 09/2019 - 12/2021

- Conducted recruitment processes including job postings, interviewing, background checks, and onboarding new hires.
- Managed employee relations issues such as grievances, performance management, disciplinary action, and terminations.
- Created training programs for new employees to help them become familiar with company culture and expectations.
- Provided guidance on policies and procedures related to employment laws and regulations.
- Coordinated with payroll department to ensure accurate processing of salaries and benefits payments.
- Maintained personnel records such as hiring documents, leaves of absence forms.

Admin Executive

Suntony Signage Pvt. Ltd., Bhubaneswar,

11/2016 - 03/2019

- Maintained protocol throughout routine work days and special events.
- Scheduled appointments and meeting, organized materials, and prepared rooms.
- Managed and organized physical and digital files, records, and documents.
- Managed incoming and outgoing communications, prioritizing emails, phone calls, and written correspondence.
- Planned and executed events for employee's clients and managed logistics and vendor relations.
- Oversaw invoices, purchase orders, and expense reports.

Internship

National Aluminum Company Limited – NALCO, Bhubaneswar.

03/2019 - 04/2019

Training and Developments.

 During my two-month internship at NALCO, I had the opportunity to immerse myself in the dynamic field of Human Resources, with a specific focus on Training and Development.